Desarrollador Full Stack

MAYERSON JIMENEZ

mayerson18@gmail.com

+57 3506208514

nayerson18

EXPERIENCIA

Company A

Developer | since January 2016

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Company B

Frontend Developer | January 2015 - December 2015

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Company C

Trainee | March 2014 - December 2014

Making coffee and baking cookies.

EDUCACIÓN

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

Master of Arts | March 2012 - December 2013

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

Bachelor of Science | March 2009 - December 2011

HABILIDADES

Also proficient in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, grew up bilingual (English and Klingon).

- Javascript
- Vue
- React

- CSS3
- Loopback
- Node.js

- TypeScript
- Angular 8
- Docker

Sobre mi

Soy desarrollador de software me especializo en la parte del frontend de paginas webs, aplicaciones tanto moviles como de escritorio, tengo experiencia en las siguientes tecnologias Html,css,javascript, vue.js(principalmente), react.js,React Native tambien tengo conocimientos en parte del backend con node.js, php y bases de datos como Mysql y mongodb.. También en pre procesadores como pug,sass y